ADRIAN TSOSIE

Albuquerque, NM · (505)967-5649

dinerodigitalconcpts@gmail.com - linkedin.com/in/adrian-tsosie-nm/ - github.com/AdrianTsosie

My whole life is about art and music. I have been in graphic design for 8 years and a DJ going on 21 years. Graphic Design has become a strong passion of mine and foresee me growing in it for years to come. In my quest to advance my skill set I immersed my in Web Development and coding and I am currently strengthening myself as a developer. With the many tools in my belt, I believe I am a great addition to where my journey my take me.

SKILLS

- Proficient in Photoshop, Illustrator, Cinema 4D,
 HTML5, CSS, MySQL, and PHP Storm.
- I am a great self-starter and love a new
- Fast learner
- Great problem solver
- Works well with team or solo challenge.

EXPERIENCE

Jan 2018 - Dec 2018

JR. DEVELOPER, DEEP DIVE BOOTCAMP

I was part of a team of 3 developers that created a web page that made it easier for people to find music events in Albuquerque. We used Html, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, and PHP Storm to make it all functional.

Jan 2018 - Dec 2018

SIGN FABRICATOR, MONARCH SIGN SYSTEMS

I was responsible for intaking orders, making sure all material for order was on hand, cutting down and building signs, and boxing up orders for shipment.

Mar 2017 - Oct 2017

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, ICONINK47 STUDI & GALLERY

I was in charge for all graphic design for the company. From advertisements, t-shirt designs, facebook up keep, and starting up and running the screen print shop.

EDUCATION

Jan 2019 - Present

FULLSTACK DEEP DIVE CODING BOOTCAMP, CNM COMMUNITY COLLEGE

Mar 2001

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, GALLUP HIGH